Jiang Yu.
We are in the same boat now.
Can't fall asleep?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just checking in on how
my partner is sleeping.
This bed is really comfortable.
Aren't you going to
invite me up, Miss Wen?
Then, you want me to
sleep on the sofa?
Don't worry.
I won't get into your bed.
Don't do this.
I won't be able to hold back.
[Dearest Episode 10]
♪ Slow embrace in the silent dark ♪
♪ Forbidden but it feels so right ♪
♪ You and me, just this one night ♪
♪ Under the faint moonlight ♪
♪ Slowly dancing, no words to say ♪
♪ Closer till we fade away ♪
♪ Taboo love in the quiet air ♪
♪ I don't care, I want you there ♪
♪ They can't know what we've begun ♪
♪ Quiet like the setting sun ♪
♪ Skin to skin, we don't make a sound ♪
♪ Lost inside the hidden round ♪
♪ We're walking on a thin, thin line ♪
♪ But I don't wanna stop this time ♪
♪ We shouldn't stay, but we don't leave ♪
♪ This quiet chemistry ♪
♪ Soft and slow, we cross the line ♪
♪ Just one more time ♪
♪ Slow embrace in the silent dark ♪
Get ready. It's time to go.
♪ Forbidden but it feels so right ♪
♪ You and me, just this one night ♪
♪ Under the faint moonlight ♪
♪ Slowly dancing, no words to say ♪
Why are you blushing?
♪ Closer till we fade away ♪
♪ Taboo love in the quiet air ♪
Hurry up.
♪ I don't care, I want you there ♪
♪ Maybe it's a sin to stay ♪
♪ But I'd lost my soul this way ♪
♪ Just your warmth against my own ♪
♪ I don't wanna go home ♪
After it's done, the fee will be doubled.
Don't worry, Mr. He.
I always do things
without leaving a trace.
You were indeed cuter when you were a kid.
It's just a fake wedding.
Do we need to pick these photos
for the VCR?
It's necessary.
If we don't take a look,
what if we get exposed?
Then, Mr. Jiang,
How long are you going to
take to pick the photos?
Are you going to look through
all these photos?
Of course.
But when you were a kid,
why did you always hold this doll?
That was a sleep-aid doll Wen Xin gave me.
When she still acted like a mother,
she used to coax me to sleep
with this doll.
So, later, without this doll,
I couldn't even fall asleep.
Then, where is
this doll now?
She cut it up when she was drunk
and out of control.
After that,
I never slept well.
It doesn't matter.
These photos are not important.
But you,
why don't you let me see your album?
Could it be that
there are photos of your old love?
You think too much.
In all my life,
I've only loved one person,
and we're not even together.
Why?
You are the boss of Cloudsea.
Why don't you go find her?
Even if she's with someone else,
you can take her by force,
force her back to your side,
and let love grow over time.
If you really love someone,
you don't have to
ask the one to love you.
But I will be prepared.
When I meet her again,
I will give her money, power, status,
and everything she wants.
That's really touching.
I'm sorry for putting you through
this fake wedding.
I'll go prepare first.
Take your time to pack.
This is our route to the wedding venue.
He Mu plans to create an explosion
at this curve we must pass
to reach the wedding venue.
Mr. Alex,
I've already dealt with He Mu for you.
Then, the business you promised me...
Don't worry.
As long as you cooperate with me,
this casino is yours.
Akun has already given me
all the information
about their transactions.
The driver has also been
replaced by our man.
So, when we get to this curve,
there will be two identical cars here.
You transfer to this car
and go safely to the wedding venue.
What about you?
I'll wait at the crime scene in advance
and let the reporters
photograph me coming out of there
when the explosion happens.
Then, at the wedding,
in front of all the guests,
I'll live-stream the explosion.
And I'll announce
all the evidence of
He Mu's murder-for-hire.
This is not just a simple
live-streamed murder case.
It's also a family tragedy caused by
the Wen family's live-in son-in-law,
who let his son approach
the Wen family's daughter
and then kill her
to seize power.
Grandpa hates the one
who tries to seize power the most.
Even if he wants to clear his name,
Grandpa won't let him succeed.
He will eventually lose everything
and never be able to make a comeback.